A Guide to the William and Flora Hewlett Foundation records FA1501
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Bay Area School Reform Collaborative (BASRC), 1994-2004; 10; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
  - Sustaining Change: A Regional Intermediary Strategy for Supporting School Reform in the Bay Area, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 549)
  - Assessing Results: Bay Area School Reform Collaborative, Year Four, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 550)
  - High School Study: Preliminary Report - Stacy Beese, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 551)
  - BASRC Evaluation Design Overview, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 552)
  - Evaluating BASRC Leadership Schools. Progress on SAT-9: Regional Comparisons and BASRC Effects - Talbert, Lin, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 553)
  - Hewlett-Annenberg-BASRC Contract, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 554)
  - Leadership Funding Memos, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 555)
  - Building Learning Communities in Schools: Request for Proposals, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 556)
  - Bay Area Support Providers, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 557)
  - Meeting Agenda, 2001 January 30 (Box 46, Folder 558)
  - Evaluation Cost Assessment, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 559)
  - Funder's Forum, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 560)
  - Phase 2 Evaluation Meeting, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 561)
  - Leadership School Monthly Mailing Update, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 562)
  - Meeting on 2002-2006 Budget, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 563)
  - Evaluation Phase 2, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 564-565)
  - Notes, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 566)
  - MDRC's Design Plan for BASRC Evaluation, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 567)
  - Bay Area School Reform Collaborative: Phase One (1995-2001) Evaluation, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 568)
  - Interim Report, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 569)
  - MDRC-CRC BASRC Evaluation Design Retreat, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 570-571)
  - Interim Report, 2002 August 28 (Box 48, Folder 572)
  - Newsletters and Annual Report, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 573)
  - Summary Report, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 574)
  - Evaluation Material, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 575)
  - Business Plan, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 576)
  - Final Report, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 577)
  - Interim Report, 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 578)
  - Planning Mid-Term Review, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 579)
  - Board Retreat Material, 2003 March 27 (Box 48, Folder 580)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 581)
  - School District Updates, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 582)
  - Board Retreat Material, 2003 April 17 (Box 48, Folder 583)
  - Just for the Kids Partnership, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 584)
  - Board Preparation Material, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 585)
  - Mid-Point Review, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 586)
  - Board Meeting Material, 2003 October 9 (Box 48, Folder 587)
  - Annual Report, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 588)
  - Strategic Planning Report, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 589)
  - Board Meeting, 2004 February 18 (Box 49, Folder 590)
  - Interim Report, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 591)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2004 March 19 (Box 49, Folder 592)
  - Board Meeting, 2004 April 17 (Box 49, Folder 593)
  - Board Retreat, 2004 April 15-16 (Box 49, Folder 594)
  - Business Plan Meeting, 2004 May 12 (Box 49, Folder 595)
  - Business Plan 2004-2008 (Box 49, Folder 596)
  - Board Meeting, 2004 May 14 (Box 49, Folder 597)
  - Board Meeting, 2004 June 22 (Box 49, Folder 598)
  - Board Meeting, 2004 August 24 (Box 49, Folder 599)
  - California Best Practices Study, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 600-601)
  - Evaluation Meeting, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 602)
- San Francisco Bay Area Performance Space, 1986-2012; 11; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
  - Space for the Arts Study - Laurie MacDougall, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 603)
  - Hewlett Foundation Recipient Summaries - Circuit Network, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 604)
  - ArtsMarket Correspondence, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 605)
  - Studies and the City, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 606)
  - Art Space Organizations, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 607)
  - Art Space Models and Solutions, 2000-2002 (Box 50, Folder 608)
  - Partnership for Affordable Non-Profit Space (PANS), 2000-2002 (Box 50, Folder 609)
  - Partnership for Affordable Non-Profit Space (PANS) - Meeting Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 50, Folder 610)
  - Partnership for Affordable Non-Profit Space (PANS) - orgSPACES.org, 2000-2002 (Box 50, Folder 611)
  - Partnership for Affordable Non-Profit Space (PANS) - Art Spaces, 2000-2001 (Box 50, Folder 612)
  - Artspace Projects, Inc. - Contract, 2000-2001 (Box 50, Folder 613)
  - Artspace Projects, Inc. - Brochures and Budget, 1999-2002 (Box 50, Folder 614)
  - San Francisco Cultural Facilities Fund, 1999-2000 (Box 50, Folder 615)
  - Compass Point Study, 2000-2004 (Box 51, Folder 616)
  - Part III: The Project on Good Work in Theatre - Year 2 Progress Report to the William and Flora Hewlett Foundation and the Ford Foundation, 2001 June (Box 51, Folder 617)
  - Artspace Projects, Inc. - Clippings, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 618)
  - San Jose Symphony, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 619)
  - San Jose Arts Fund, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 620)
  - Mountain View Community School of Music and Art, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 621-622)
  - Tannery Arts Center - Correspondence, 1999-2006 (Box 51, Folder 623)
  - Survey of Artists Space Needs in Santa Cruz and San Jose, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 624)
  - Tannery Arts Center - Plan Presentation, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 625-626)
  - Tannery Arts Center - Mataraza Plan, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 627)
  - 9th Street Media Center - Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 52, Folder 628)
  - 9th Street Media Center - Lease and Amendments, 2001-2002 (Box 52, Folder 629)
  - Mid-Market Redevelopment, 2001-2002 (Box 52, Folder 630)
  - Fort Mason Center, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 631-632)
  - Investing in Creativity: A Study of the Support Structure for U.S. Artists - The Urban Institute, 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 633)
  - Spotlight - LINES and San Francisco Dance Center Three Year Transition Plan, 2001-2002 (Box 53, Folder 634)
  - National Cultural Facilities Study - Final Report, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 635)
  - Tannery Arts Center - Photo Book, undated (Box 53, Folder 636)
  - Continental Harmony: A Study in Community-Based Arts, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 637)
  - Continental Harmony - Radio Documentaries Disk 1 of 3 (Box 53, Folder 637)
  - Nonprofits at Risk: The Space and Occupancy Crisis Facing San Francisco's Nonprofit Community, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 638)
  - The Market for a San Francisco Nonprofit Multi-Tenant Project - A Study for the Charles and Helen Schwab Foundation, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 639)
  - A Management Audit of the Center for the Arts at Yerba Buena Gardens - Melanie Beene, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 640)
  - Downtown Berkeley Public Improvements Plan, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 641)
  - Bay Area Regional Performing Arts Facilities Study, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 642)
  - Land Use and the California Economy: Principles for Prosperity and Quality of Life, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 643)
  - California Arts Organizations: How Are They Affected by Rent and Labor Costs #97-1443, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 644)
  - Involving Youth in Nonprofit Arts Organizations, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 645)
  - 1994-1995 Orchestra Survey Report - Association of California Symphony Orchestras (Box 54, Folder 646)
  - The William and Flora Hewlett Foundation's Performing Arts Program - Recommendations for the Diagnosis and Treatment of Financial Distress in Nonprofit Performing Arts Organizations - Oakland Symphony Case Study, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 647)
  - The State of Orchestral Organizations in the Bay Area, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 648)
  - Advocating for the Arts: Fundamentals, Training, and New Directions for Local Arts Agencies and Municipal Arts Programs in Alameda County, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 649)
  - Preliminary Database and Tools: Work in Progress - Haas, Hewlett, Irvine Foundations, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 650)
  - Preliminary Report on Market Conditions, Trends, and Transformations Affecting the Four Cities, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 651)
  - Third Monthly Progress Report and Analysis: The Nature of the Marketplace, the Nature of the Field - Haas, Hewlett, Irvine Foundations, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 652)
  - Fourth Monthly Progress Report: Update on Findings - Haas, Hewlett, Irvine Foundations, undated (Box 54, Folder 653)
  - Sixth Monthly Progress Report - Haas, Hewlett, Irvine Foundations, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 654)
  - California Arts Audience Research Project: Performing Arts in California - Rebuilding, Repositioning, Re-emerging - Haas, Hewlett, Irvine Foundations, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 655)
  - Hastings College of the Law - The Great Hall Performing Arts Facility - Planning Study, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 656)
  - The Great Hall Project - Analysis of Potential Users and Competing Facilities, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 657)
  - The Great Hall Project - Management Study with Recommendations, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 658)
  - Pier 70 Advisory Group, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 659)
  - Artspace, Inc. - Twentieth Anniversary Report of Progress, undated (Box 55, Folder 660)
  - Artspace, Inc. - Analysis and Viability Study of Space for the Arts in San Francisco, 2001 July (Box 56, Folder 661)
  - Artspace, Inc. - Analysis and Viability Study of Space for the Arts in San Francisco, 2001 October (Box 56, Folder 662)
  - Proposed Arts Policy for the City and County of San Francisco, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 663)
  - The Impact of the Non-Profit Arts on the Economy of San Francisco, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 664)
  - A Community Collaboration for the Arts - Silicon Valley Arts Fund, undated (Box 56, Folder 665)
  - Northern California Community Loan Fund, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 666)
  - Creativity and Neighborhood Development: Strategies for Community Investment - Nowak, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 667)
  - The Arts Advantage to California in the Changing World - California Legislature Joint Committee on the Arts, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 668)
  - Check Up: An Assessment Tool for Community Service and Cultural Organizations, undated (Box 57, Folder 669)
  - Building Community: A Report to the Baltimore Community Foundation - Boyer, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 670)
  - Creative Communities Initiative Summary Report - National Guild of Community Schools of the Arts, 2006 (Box 57, Folder 671)
  - A State Arts Agency: Performance Measurement Toolkit - The National Assembly of State Arts Agencies, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 672)
  - California Arts Initiative Public Opinion Survey, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 673)
  - Jobs, the Arts, and the Economy: Highlighting Findings from NALAA's Arts in the Local Economy Study, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 674)
  - Mobilizing Arts and Cultural Resources for Community Development, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 675)
  - Conceptual Alternatives Workbook - An Updated Plan for Area B of the Presidio, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 676)
  - Creative Community Index: Measuring Progress Toward a Vibrant Silicon Valley, undated (Box 57, Folder 677)
  - Nonprofit Finance Fund, undated (Box 57, Folder 678)
  - Exploring the Role of the Arts in the Development of Disadvantaged Communities - Conference Summary, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 679)
  - White Paper on the Economic Impact of the Arts and Culture Industry in San Jose, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 680)
  - Securing a Safe Haven: Facilities Strategies for San Francisco's Nonprofits, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 681)
  - The Values Study: Rediscovering the Meaning and Value of Arts Participation, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 682-683)
  - Re-Commissioning Management Manual - CTG Energetics, Inc., 2003 (Box 58, Folder 684)
  - Re-Commissioning Management Manual: Commissioning Report - CTG Energetics, Inc., 2003 (Box 58, Folder 685)
  - A Portrait of Race and Ethnicity in California: An Assessment of Social and Economic Well-Being - Reyes, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 686)
  - Re-engaging High School Dropouts: Early Results of the National Guard Youth Challenge Program Evaluation, 2009 (Box 58, Folder 687)
  - Birth Control - Top Picks, 2012 (Box 58, Folder 688)
  - Mayfair Neighborhood Improvement Initiative - Teamworks, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 689)
  - Kipp Schools: A Study of Early Implementation and Achievement - Final Report, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 690)
  - Community Health in Action Fellowship Program - Annual Report, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 691)
- William and Flora Hewlett Foundation Audiovisual Material, 1998-2012; 12; 1.75 Cubic Feet 3 legal document boxes and 1 oversize box
  Oral history project interviews, grant product media, and foundation-related material.
  Moving Images; Sound recordings
  - Bacchetti, Ray (1 of 2), 1999 November 19; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15450)
  - Bacchetti, Ray (2 of 2), 1999 November 19; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15451)
  - Brown, Dyke (1 of 2), 1999 October 22; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15452)
  - Brown, Dyke (2 of 2), 1999 October 22; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15453)
  - Burroughs, Hugh (1 of 2), 1999 August 4; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15454)
  - Burroughs, Hugh (2 of 2), 1999 August 4; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15455)
  - Davis, Alice DePalma (1 of 1), 1999 August 11; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15456)
  - Erburu, Robert - Addendum, 2000 June; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15457)
  - Gaither, James (1 of 2), 1999 June 18; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15458)
  - Gaither, James (2 of 2), 1999 June 18; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15459)
  - Gardner, David P. (1 of 2), 1999 November 11; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15460)
  - Gardner, David P. (2 of 2), 1999 November 11; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15461)
  - Gimon, Eleanor H. (1 of 2), 2000 January 31; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15462)
  - Gimon, Eleanor H. (2 of 2), 2000 January 31; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15463)
  - Gump, Patricia (1 of 2), 1999 November 30; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15464)
  - Gump, Patricia (2 of 2), 1999 November 30; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15465)
  - Hewlett, James (1 of 2), 1999 September 10; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15466)
  - Hewlett, James (2 of 2), 1999 September 10; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 16467)
  - Hewlett, Walter (1 of 3), 1998 November 18; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15468)
  - Hewlett, Walter (2 of 3), 1999 December 20; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15469)
  - Hewlett, Walter (3 of 3), 1999 December 20; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15470)
  - Hewlett, William A.(1 of 1), 1999 September 2; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15471)
  - Jaffe, Mary H. (1 of 2), 1999 January 2; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15472)
  - Jaffe, Mary (2 of 2), 1999 January 2; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15473)
  - Katchadourian, Herant (1 of 2), 1999 June 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15474)
  - Katchadourian, Herant (2 of 2), 1999 June 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15475)
  - Lobman, Ted (1 of 3), 1999 August 21; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15476)
  - Lobman, Ted (2 of 3), 1999 August 21; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15477)
  - Lobman, Ted (3 of 3), 1999 August 21; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15478)
  - Miller, Arjay (1 of 2), 1999 June 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15479)
  - Miller, Arjay (2 of 2), 1999 June 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15480)
  - Murray, Anne Firth (1 of 3), 1999 September 10; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15481)
  - Murray, Anne Firth (2 of 3), 1999 September 10; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15482)
  - Murray, Anne Firth (3 of 3), 1999 September 10; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15483)
  - Nichols, William (1 of 2), 1999 November 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15484)
  - Nichols, William (2 of 2), 1999 November 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15485)
  - Pallotti, Marianne (1 of 2), 1999 January 22; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15486)
  - Pallotti, Marianne (2 of 2), 1999 January 22; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15487)
  - Penny, Alvertha (1 of 2), 1999 November 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15488)
  - Penny, Alvertha (2 of 2), 1999 November 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15489)
  - Schaps, Eric (1 of 1), 1999 November 12; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15490)
  - Toben, Stephen (2 of 2), 1999 November 18; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15491)
  - Generic Classroom B-Roll - Learning Matters, Inc., VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11848)
  - NewsHour with Jim Lehrer Footage for the William and Flora Hewlett Foundation: Smiling Faces from the Developing World, Classroom Slots, Scenes from the West, Betacam SP (Box 2, Tape AV 11849)
  - Underwriting Spot #2 Education, Betacam SP (Box 2, Tape AV 11850)
  - National Campaign to Prevent Teen Pregnancy - Media Reel Highlights, VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11851)
  - Deep Dive, VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11852)
  - Fathers Too Soon - Produced in Association with Channel One Network, VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11853)
  - FRONTLINE/World Stories to Hewlett Foundation: Coffee Country - Guatemala, Hole in the Wall - India, Kids Shots - South Africa, VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11854)
  - Advocates for Youth - News and Entertainment Media Clips (1), 2000; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11855)
  - Advocates for Youth - News and Entertainment Media Clips (2), VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11856)
  - A Walk in Your Shoes - Teen Parent, VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11857)
  - Hewlett Foundation 1998 Retreat at Chaminade, VHS (Box 3, Tape AV 11858)
  - Hewlett Foundation April '98 Retreat at Chaminade, 1998; VHS (Box 3, Tape AV 11859)
  - LinkTV - UN Millennium Goals Reel, VHS (Box 3, Tape AV 11860)
  - Planet Campaign TV Spots, VHS (Box 3, Tape AV 11861)
  - International News Coverage in America: The Angry World, moderated by Terrance Smith - Complete TV Version, 2003-2004; VHS; 57 minutes (Box 3, Tape AV 11862)
  - International News Coverage in America: The Angry World, moderated by Terrance Smith - Southern Newspaper Publishers Association Version, 2003-2004; VHS; 30 minutes (Box 3, Tape AV 11863)
  - Preventing Teenage Pregnancy - Ricki Lake, 2003 May 7; VHS (Box 3, Tape AV 11864)
  - Mothers Too Soon - Produced in Association with Channel One Network, VHS (Box 3, Tape AV 11865)
  - The Right-Wing Message Machine, VHS (Box 3, Tape AV 11866)
  - Wide Angle: Red Lines and Deadlines - Thirteen WNET New York, VHS (Box 3, Tape AV 11867)
  - NewsHour Promo Reel, 2004; VHS (Box 3, Tape AV 11868)
  - First to Worst, 2004 (Box 3, Tape AV 11869)
  - Middle School Confessions - HSP HBO Studio Productions, VHS; 74 minutes (Box 3, Tape AV 11870)
  - Scenarios USA - Choices: The Good, The Bad, The Ugly, VHS (Box 4, Tape AV 11871)
  - Scenarios USA - From an Objective Point of View: Today I Found Out, VHS (Box 4, Tape AV 11872)
  - Scenarios USA - Lipstick, VHS (Box 4, Tape AV 11873)
  - Scenarios USA - Just Like You Imagined?, VHS (Box 4, Tape AV 11874)
  - How Do You Spell God? - Part 1 - HSP HBO Studio Productions, 32 minutes; VHS (Box 4, Tape AV 11875)
  - Voices of Choice - Physicians Who Provided Abortions Before Roe v. Wade, VHS; 25 minutes (Box 4, Tape AV 11876)
  - Wide Angle: Ladies First - Thirteen WNET New York, VHS; 57 minutes (Box 4, Tape AV 11877)
  - John Gardner: Uncommon American, 2000; VHS; 57 minutes (Box 4, Tape AV 11878)
    Narrated by Richard Dreyfuss.
  - Wide Angle: Time for School - Thirteen WNET New York, VHS; 57 minutes (Box 4, Tape AV 11879)
  - The Act of Teaching - Part 1: Theatre Techniques for Classroom Presentations, 2001; VHS; 44 minutes (Box 4, Tape AV 11880)
  - The Act of Teaching - Part 2: Physical and Vocal Exercises, 2001; VHS; 15 minutes (Box 4, Tape AV 11881)
  - Wide Angle: Coca and the Congressman - Thirteen WNET New York, VHS; 57 minutes (Box 4, Tape AV 11882)
  - Paul Brest Farewell DVD, 2012 August 30
  - Paul Brest MP4, 2012 August 30
  - What Does A Grant Sound Like? A Holiday Mix Featuring Music By Hewlett Foundation Grantees, 1994
    1. The Sonos Handbell Ensemble: Water Music (Handel, arr. J. Meredith)
    2. Kronos Quartet: Mini Skirt (Esquivel)
    3. Rova: Juke Box Afro Balkan (Jon Raskin)
    4. Crosspulse: I Like the Way You Move (OutKast)
    5. Kitka: Shto Mi E Milo (Live at Ashkenaz)
    6. Philharmonia Baroque Orchestra: Violin Concerto in D Major (Beethoven)
    7. Los Cenzontle: Pasajero (Julian Gonzalez)
    8. Other Minds: Theme Park (Alvin Curran)
    9. San Jose Jazz Society: Take the A Train (Ellington)
    10. San Francisco Girls Chorus: Picking the Seed Pods (Chen Yi)
    11. Oakland Youth Orchestra: It Don't Mean A Thing (Ellington)
  - Steve Neal Video Clip regarding Paul Brest
  - Interviews/Disc One - Steve Neal, Herant Katchadourian, Koh Boon Hwee, 2012 July 21
  - Interviews/Disc Two - Arjay Miller, Paul Brest, 2012 July 21
  - Council on Foundations Philanthropy's Vision: A Leadership Summit, Washington Metropolitan Area - Strategic Philanthropy: Theory and Practice, Paul Brest, Meeting # FO0801, Session Number 64, 2008 May 4-7
  - Board Interviews Files
  - Campana Magnificus Video - Susan Bell Tribute, 2012 June
  - Jim Canales - James Irvine Foundation, 2012 July
  - Fostering Collective Impact: Mexico Case Study (Final Mexico COP Video with Credit Changes - Janet Jarman), 2012 January 30
  - Andrew Carnegie Medal of Philanthropy and International Philanthropy Symposium, Scottish Parliament, Scotland (Disk 1 - Welcome), 2005 October 4
  - Andrew Carnegie Medal of Philanthropy and International Philanthropy Symposium, Scottish Parliament, Scotland (Disk 2 - Medal Ceremony), 2005 October 4
  - Andrew Carnegie Medal of Philanthropy and International Philanthropy Symposium, Scottish Parliament, Scotland (Disk 3 - Poverty and Health), 2005 October 4
  - Andrew Carnegie Medal of Philanthropy and International Philanthropy Symposium, Scottish Parliament, Scotland (Disk 4 - Environment and Sustainable Development), 2005 October 4
  - Andrew Carnegie Medal of Philanthropy and International Philanthropy Symposium, Scottish Parliament, Scotland (Disk 5 - Education), 2005 October 4
  - Andrew Carnegie Medal of Philanthropy and International Philanthropy Symposium, Scottish Parliament, Scotland (Disk 6 - International Peace, Justice and Security), 2005 October 4
  - Andrew Carnegie Medal of Philanthropy and International Philanthropy Symposium, Scottish Parliament, Scotland (Disk 7 - Democracy, Governance and Civil Society), 2005 October 4
  - Andrew Carnegie Medal of Philanthropy and International Philanthropy Symposium, Scottish Parliament, Scotland (Disk 8 - Legal, Fiscal and Governance), 2005 October 4
  - The Hewlett Foundation Retreat at Chaminade, 1998
  - Lecture on the History on the Hewlett Foundation - Hewlett Foundation Retreat at Chaminade, 1998
  - Wari le Magazine Economique - l'emission diffusee, 2009 May 31
- Oversize Material, 2005-2012; 13; 0.79 Cubic Feet 1 half-legal document box and 2 oversize boxes
  - Hewlett Challenge Celebration Book, 2012 November 3 (Box 59)
  - California State Senate to The Center for the Future of Teaching and Learning Resolution, 2006 August 15 (Box 60)
  - Appreciation Poster to Robert F. Erburu, 2005 October 16 (Box 61)